embarrassingproblems.com 2014-05-16

# Privacy on our site

Health Press Limited is committed to protecting the privacy of embarrassingproblems.com users. Below is information outlining our continued support for the responsible management of user information. Please leave the site if you do not agree to the terms below.

##  Comments

Before submitting a Comment, Health Press Limited will request username (optional), age, sex and country of residence. The information provided is used to improve the content of the site. In order to provide the website and Comments, any data provided may be seen by third parties, such as our digital agency staff. Do remember that any information you reveal in a public forum such as the Comments, including personally identifiable information, is not subject to this Privacy Policy and can be seen by third parties unrelated to Health Press Limited - please carefully consider what information you disclose in these areas. Information from our Comments is stored in archives until the corresponding page is updated.

##  Cookies

Our web pages use cookies. We use cookies to understand site usage and to improve the content and offerings on our site. Health Press Limited may use the aggregated information to study statistical results and produce summary reports. Such reports may be shared with Health Press Limited's partners and advertisers, but the reports will not disclose personally identifiable information. Except from that stated above, Health Press Limited will not disclose any of your personally identifiable information without your permission except under special circumstances, for instance if Health Press Limited in good faith believes that the law requires disclosure. Any information collected by Health Press Limited will be treated confidentially.

**Turning cookies on or off in your browser**

You have a number of options when it comes to receiving cookies. You can set your browser either to reject all cookies, to allow only ‘trusted’ sites to send them, or to accept only those cookies from websites you are currently using.We recommend that you don’t block all cookies because parts of our website rely on them to work properly.

To find out how to turn cookies on and off in your browser, click on your browser’s link below.

  * [Google Chrome  
](http://support.google.com/chrome/bin/answer.py?hl=en&answer=95647)
  * [Mozilla FireFox  
](http://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/Enabling%20and%20disabling%20cookies)
  * [Apple Safari  
](http://docs.info.apple.com/article.html?path=Safari/5.0/en/9277.html)
  * [Apple Safari for iOS  
](http://support.apple.com/kb/HT1677)
  * [Microsoft Internet Explorer  
](http://windows.microsoft.com/en-US/windows7/Block-enable-or-allow-cookies)
  * [Google Android  
](http://support.google.com/mobile/bin/answer.py?hl=en&answer=169022)

##  External links

Embarrassingproblems.com contains links to other site. Please note that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. Users should be aware when they leave our site and read the privacy statements of each and every website collecting personally identifiable information.

##  Updates

Updates to our Privacy Policy will be posted here so that our users always know what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We will use the information in accordance with the Privacy Policy under which the information was collected.
